<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>france on BeyondF1</title>
    <link>https://beyondf1.netlify.app/tags/france/</link>
    <description>Recent content in france on BeyondF1</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 11:28:41 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://beyondf1.netlify.app/tags/france/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Binotto says Ferrari’s Paul Ricard struggles stemmed from issues ‘two years ago that we should have addressed’</title>
      <link>https://beyondf1.netlify.app/binotto-says-ferrari-s-paul-ricard-struggles-stemmed-from-issues-two-years-ago-that-we-should-have-addressed/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 11:28:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beyondf1.netlify.app/binotto-says-ferrari-s-paul-ricard-struggles-stemmed-from-issues-two-years-ago-that-we-should-have-addressed/</guid>
      <description>Ferrari Team Principal Mattia Binotto admitted after a ‘very tiring and difficult’ French Grand Prix that the team’s disastrous result – with Carlos Sainz in P11 and Charles Leclerc in P16 – hadn’t been entirely unexpected, with the conditions at Paul Ricard having exposed a weakness that Ferrari have been aware of for several years, according to Binotto.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>‘We gambled, we lost’ – Wolff explains why Mercedes stuck with one-stop strategy in France</title>
      <link>https://beyondf1.netlify.app/we-gambled-we-lost-wolff-explains-why-mercedes-stuck-with-one-stop-strategy-in-france/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 11:27:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beyondf1.netlify.app/we-gambled-we-lost-wolff-explains-why-mercedes-stuck-with-one-stop-strategy-in-france/</guid>
      <description>Mercedes’ hopes of winning the French Grand Prix were undone by Red Bull adopting a surprise two-stop strategy – but why didn’t the Silver Arrows try the same thing at Paul Ricard? Team Principal Toto Wolff explained all after the scintillating race.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6 Winners and 5 Losers from the French GP – Who brought their A-game to Paul Ricard?</title>
      <link>https://beyondf1.netlify.app/6-winners-and-5-losers-from-the-french-gp-who-brought-their-a-game-to-paul-ricard/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 11:24:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://beyondf1.netlify.app/6-winners-and-5-losers-from-the-french-gp-who-brought-their-a-game-to-paul-ricard/</guid>
      <description>There was elation in the Red Bull garage as Max Verstappen executed an aggressive strategy to snatch victory from Lewis Hamilton on the penultimate lap, leaving rivals Mercedes with plenty to do as they left Paul Ricard, a venue that had been considered a Silver Arrows fortress. It was an enthralling battle up front, but there was plenty of excitement further down the field. We’ve picked out six winners and five losers from Sunday’s race</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
